isport.com.au 2007-07-17

# Protecting your privacy

                                       Multibase WebAustralis Pty Ltd
                                            ACN 063 962 916 ABN 54 063 962 916
                                          Protecting your privacy
The main business of Multibase WebAustralis is to develop, market, deliver and support technology
products and services.
Multibase WebAustralis privacy policy
Multibase WebAustralis (Multibase) is committed to protecting your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy
outlines the type of information that is collected by Multibase, and how we use and protect it. The policy tells
you what to do if you do not want your personal information collected, and how you can change information
you have already provided to us. This policy applies only to the business information that we collect and to
our web site. Our customers’ web sites are covered by separate policies.
Multibase complies with the Privacy Act 1988 (Commonwealth) and any code approved by the Privacy
Commissioner under section 18BB of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). This includes the National Privacy
Principles introduced on 21 December, 2001.
Your consent to this privacy policy
By using our services, including our web site, you say that you agree with the terms of our current Privacy
Policy as described in this document. If you do not agree with any part of this Policy, it is not possible to use
our services.
Collection of personal information
As used in this Privacy Policy, 'personal information' means personally identifiable information such as your
name, street address, email address, telephone number, and credit card information.
When you request a product or service from us, or inquire about our products and services, you may be
asked to provide personal information so that you can buy a product or service from us, receive information
or mailings, request customer support, make a comment or enquiry or for a variety of other reasons.
When you provide us with personal information, you are authorising us to use that information in accordance
with the terms of this Privacy Policy, which includes your right to limit our use of the personal information
(see Who to Contact below).
We may supplement the information that you provide to us with other information we hold already or that we
receive from third parties. We do this in order to manage the services and products that we provide to you.
We also may do this for marketing purposes in order to provide more targeted products and service to meet
your needs.
How we collect information about you, and how we use it
Product and service information: If you have purchased products or services from Multibase, we will hold
your contact details as well as details of the services that we provide to you and the use that you make of
those services. Those details are primarily used to manage the service that we provide, to send you
information about the relevant products, or any upgrades that become available, latest developments, and
forthcoming events.
Technical Support: If you contact Multibase Customer Service, or seek online support from us, we will hold
your contact details and, if you have paid for a service, your credit card or other payment details. We
generally keep a record of the problem that you report and any actions that we recommend.
Information for marketing: If we have collected your details from an enquiry you made or because we think
you may be interested in one of our products or services, we will hold your contact details and details of
information that send to you. The personal information we hold is used to communicate with you on the
topics you have indicated an interest in or that we believe that you may be interested in.
All of the above information is stored on our internal systems, not on a publicly accessible server.
When you visit a page: When you visit our web site, or a web site hosted on our web servers, the web
server will track the IP address you come from (a number assigned to your computer whenever you connect
                      Level 1, 11-17 Khartoum Rd, Macquarie Park, NSW 2113 Australia
                                  PO Box 1989 Macquarie Centre NSW 2113
  Tel: +61 2 9805 1911 Fax: +61 2 9805 1931 Email: info@mbase.com.au Web: www.mbase.com.au

to the Internet), what URL you came from, the browser type and computing platform you are using, which
pages were requested, and the duration of your session. The only way that we can connect this with any
individual information about you is if you buy something from our site, in which case we may connect the IP
address you came from with some personal information.
We may use this information to analyse the way that site visitors use our site, in order to improve our site
and the services that we offer.
Sometimes we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web
sites. We also use this information to track which areas of our sites users use and don't use based on traffic
to those areas. We do not as a matter of course use this to track what individual users read, but rather how
well each page or section of the site performs overall.
Occasionally, in order to troubleshoot a problem with a web application such as a shopping cart, we review a
web server log to identify the pages that a particular user viewed in a web site.
Public Forums: Multibase web sites may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups
available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public
information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Cookies: A cookie is a small data file that certain web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A
cookie file contains information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the
only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data
off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.
Some Multibase web sites use cookies to collect other information during your visit to our web site, such as
the particular site areas you visit and the products or services you buy through our web site. Cookies may
also be used to help speed up your future activities at our site. For example, a site can recognise that you
have provided Personal Information to use and refrain from requesting the same information a second time.
Most browsers are initially set to accept a cookie. If you'd prefer you can set your browser to refuse cookies
or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Refusal of cookies at the site you enter may result in an inability
to visit certain areas of the site or to receive personalised information when you visit the site.
We collect this information to better tailor our site and our products to your interests and needs.
Multibase and other web sites: Some Multibase sites are operated jointly with or on behalf of other
reputable organisations. For example, Multibase operates the iSport Australasia web sites. These sites may
offer special terms and conditions that differ from Multibase’s standard terms and conditions, which may
handle your personal information differently. If different privacy policies apply, they will be available on those
web sites. If they are our contractors, that are bound by our privacy policies.
Multibase sites and these other sites may contain links to websites outside of the services that we provide.
These linked sites are not under the control of Multibase, and we are not responsible for the conduct of
companies linked to our web site. Before disclosing your personal information on any other web site, we
advise you to examine the terms and conditions of using their web sites.
Your information and third parties
Your personal information and the information we gather through the products and services that we provide
to you are used by Multibase for the express purpose for which it was collected. It may also be used by us to
improve our products, services, business processes, product collateral etc, and to contact you regarding
other products and services which may be of interest to you (including those we may offer jointly with other
companies). At any time you may opt out of such future contact. (See Who to Contact below.)
We do not provide personal information to other companies except where they are subcontractors or
suppliers directly involved in the delivery of your product or service. We do not provide your personal
information to third parties to use for their own marketing purposes.
Our subcontractors and suppliers are bound by our privacy policy and by confidentiality agreements, and are
not authorised by us to use your personal information in any other way. At any time you may request
information about the suppliers or subcontractors involved in the provision of your products or services.
Please note that we will release your personal information if required to do so by law, or by search warrant,
subpoena or court order.
Security of information
We take reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure. Access to your personal
information is permitted among our employees only on a need-to-know basis.
If the personal information that we have about you is no longer needed for the purposes stated in this
privacy policy, we will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information.
 G:\Marketing\Privacy\Multibase_privacy.doc                                                                   Page 2

All our staff are trained in the importance of protecting your personal information, and in the methods by
which we do so. Our staff are bound by confidentiality agreements to keep your personal information secure.
In certain cases, certain Multibase staff or contractors may have access to information about our customers
or information about our customer’s clients. This information is considered confidential, and staff are trained
and supervised in privacy principles and procedures, and operate under confidentiality agreements.
Multibase has checks and balances in place covering who has access to this information, and there are
safeguards to ensure that this information is protected against misuse or loss, and from unauthorised
access, modification or disclosure. Should the situation arise, we will comply with all reasonable directions
from our clients in respect of dealing with their confidential or personal Information including returning or
destroying the information.
Accuracy of information
Multibase takes reasonable steps to make sure that the personal information that we collect, use or disclose
is accurate, complete and up to date. From time to time, we may contact you to check that our information is
accurate.
Access to your personal information
Multibase will provide you with reasonable access to the personal information that we hold about you,
except where doing so would contravene the National Privacy Principles. If providing this information would
impose unreasonable costs on Multibase, we will advise you of the reasons for this and that a reasonable
charge will be imposed to obtain the information for you.
If you can establish that the information about you is not accurate, complete and up to date, we will take
reasonable steps to correct this information.
Complaint handling procedure
If you have a complaint about breaches of this Privacy Policy, in the first instance please contact Multibase
in one of the ways below.
Multibase will investigate your complaint, with reference to Part V of the Privacy Act. If you are not satisfied
with the way that we respond to your complaint, your next step is to refer your complaint to the Office of the
Federal Privacy Commissioner. The complaint will then be dealt with as determined by the Privacy
Commissioner.
Changes in our policy
Multibase reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at our discretion. If we decide to change our
Privacy Policy we will post those changes on our web site. We encourage you to visit this site frequently to
stay informed.
Who to contact
Please write to us by one of the means below if you have any comments or questions about this Privacy
Statement or to report any breaches of the Privacy Policy. We will respond to you within 2 business days in
most cases.
Multibase is committed to protecting your privacy. Please do not hesitate to contact us if you have any
questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy.
Multibase WebAustralis Pty Ltd ACN 063 962 916 ABN 41 063 962 916
Level 1, 11-17 Khartoum Rd, Macquarie Park NSW 2113
PO Box 1989 Macquarie Centre NSW 2113
Telephone:             02 9805 1911 Fax: 02 9805 1931
Email:                 customerservice@mbase.com.au
Web:                   www.mbase.com.au
 G:\Marketing\Privacy\Multibase_privacy.doc                                                                  Page 3
